want to get immediate benefits from your
policy instead of only at the point of
claim at FWD we believe in letting our
policy holders enjoy benefits right from
the start we bring you our exclusive FWD
Health first program made available to
all our protection plan policy
holders the benefits of FWD Health First
include access to free teleconsultation
with an experienced healthc care
professional
24/7 teleconsultation medicine delivered
conveniently to your doorstep at only $5
preferred rates at over 600 MHC general
practitioner and dental clinics there's
more you can extend these benefits to
your spouse children parents and even
grandparents ensuring that your family's
health care cost remain affordable
here's how to get started scan the QR
code if you're already an FWD protection
plan policy holder or simply purchase a
protection policy today FWD Health first
program caring for you and the people
you care for get these benefits
now